so I was sitting here trying to figure
out what to do today's video on and none
of the normal YouTube videos I'm
watching that are released weekly are
speaking to me I don't want to do a
response on them and after my new if the
news feed comes a TED talk that looked
interesting and I clicked on it turns
out I've seen it before but it was
supposed to today so it's entitled
isolation is the dream killer not your
attitude by Barbara Sher and it talks
about how it's in the title how shocks
what this guy named Ronnie who is just a
really unlikable human but this group
helps him find an apartment and a
girlfriend and of course changes his
life and how she goes on to do this same
activity in a larger group with over and
over and over again and the times the
kinds of dreams that are helped come
into being in a large group and she
talks about how all you need to do is
state your wish and your obstacle and
somebody will be able to help you and I
love that and I realize even back when I
first saw this video what I wanted to do
is create an app with that and that's my
wish my wish is always can we create an
app that we all own together that
society can focus on and if we created
such an app that helps people focus on
like a Pinterest but actually helps your
dream come true
here is my wish here is my obstacle and
other people hear that and and
problem-solve the solution for you just
that would help change humanity in so
many ways and I've seen that happen
online again again where someone's
having a rough time and somebody has the
solution somebody can't afford groceries
and without I even asking just kind of
venting about it people step forward to
help people step forward to help with
childcare you know I haven't a plan that
my husband and I childcare cancel hey
where do you live with watch your child
for you people want to help we just have
to get the right people to the right
places and what she says is we depend on
each other's dreams coming true when
your dream comes true when somebody
else's dream comes true
it echoes into the world in a very
particular wonderful way and that is
foundationally what I am talking about
when I talk about creating the global
cooperative I know I talk about it
sometimes in a more negative language
like we're gonna dismantle capitalism
but that does dismantle capitalism it's
based on having people have unfulfilled
which wishes and obstacles they can
surmount and have to pay money to
surrounds it have to like fill holes and
voids in their in their selves the cats
are not listening to not interrupting
and so that's today's video I I'm still
the focus is on creating the
conversation out because from the
conversation app all of these things can
take place but creating a wish obstacle
app so that we can help each other's
dreams come true would be amazing anyone
want to do it I'm all for it take my
idea and run with it please like and
subscribe